{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37d91aa448170017a2fd7c"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"New","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941146463"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941146463"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d0b68dfe868d30017988c64"},"name":"Sasi Kiran Vanapalli","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Context setting and scope","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Almost covered as per the scope","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1.5 Months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Yet to use the product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, Day 2 is a bit slow due to complex topics but overall it is good","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561028831209"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561028831209"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d0bb89b09585e0017b5d387"},"name":"Divya Chandra","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Aspice content though looks simple but in reality it is confusing and takes time to settle down. L1, L2 , L3 concept repition throughtout the training was helpful."}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Difference between different levels of Aspice.  ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Mostly covered everything. Coverage of topics was relevant and good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":"scope of applying currently is the biggest challenge with EB India. "},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"There was lot of efforts put in to get all the information and flow together for this training. Thanks to the entire Quality team.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561049243391"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561049243391"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d11a38a490a580017338156"},"name":"","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3","comments":"3"},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3","comments":"3"}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":"4"},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":"4"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561437066603"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561437066603"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d11a5af490a580017338157"},"name":"Rasna","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Came to know in which level our project stands"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Got an overview about ASPICE standards and levels","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Could have been better if Level 4 and level 5 are explained more in detailed","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"0","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Currently not using any EB product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561437615423"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561437615423"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d11b4fc93ce7900177d6769"},"name":"","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"I liked the way the learnings were imparted and co-related through the activities"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Introduction and management section","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Yet to start using ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561441532146"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561441532146"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d11eff7e1e3280017969973"},"name":"","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Got complete ASPICE overview "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":" ASPICE  levels ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Most of  the thing are covered ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"User experience","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561456631002"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561456631002"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d1ed5aa2a65fe001702cb72"},"name":"Nimisha","training":"EB Tresos Studio Training","trainers":"Anbarasan Annadurai,Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Continental","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"1","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"1","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"1","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Test Comment"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"abc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"abc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"abc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"abc","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"1","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1562301866911"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1562301866911"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d26f3a8026a790017b1165b"},"name":"Sebastian Nitu","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Elektrobit","date":"2019-07-26 to 2019-07-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Everything "}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Introduction ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"4 years","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Development","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833832798"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833832798"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d26f3ab026a790017b1165c"},"name":"Christian","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Elektrobit","date":"2019-07-26 to 2019-07-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":"sdfsdf"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"0","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"1","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"sdfsdfas"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"gjhguilfzui","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"eduzedtz","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"fghjfgjh","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"ghjgjh","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"statement","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833835628"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833835628"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d26f3b4026a790017b1165d"},"name":"Sowmya P","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Elektrobit","date":"2019-07-26 to 2019-07-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Demo session"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"demo","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"None","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"2","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Module","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833844860"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833844860"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d26f3d1026a790017b1165e"},"name":"","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Elektrobit","date":"2019-07-26 to 2019-07-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"0","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"0","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"0","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833873749"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833873749"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d26f400026a790017b1165f"},"name":"Dorleta Gonzalez","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Elektrobit","date":"2019-07-26 to 2019-07-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":"okkkk"}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"the smile"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"the product","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"nothing","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"fjdlkfja","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":"rgsdrgsth"}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833920759"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833920759"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d26f40f026a790017b11660"},"name":"Divya","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Elektrobit","date":"2019-07-26 to 2019-07-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833935768"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833935768"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d26f429026a790017b11661"},"name":"Jochen","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Elektrobit","date":"2019-07-26 to 2019-07-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"3","comments":"ÄÖÜßñ"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":"How much text is possible here?"}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Of course.\n","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833961142"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1562833961142"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d39c8cab5e7180017b589ea"},"name":"","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Elektrobit","date":"2019-07-26 to 2019-07-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"0","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"0","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"0","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1564068042876"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1564068042876"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d0b22060bde880017a672e6"},"name":"Ashwini Kamalesh","training":"ASPICE","trainers":"Sowmya,Manushree","location":"EB Internal","date":"2019-06-19 to 2019-06-20","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"We had overview session by Sowmya for Validation team."},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. Got an overview of the ASPICE.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1561010694665"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1561010694665"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37d809a448170017a2fd7a"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Information"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Exercise","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Diagnostics (DCM, DEM in depth), component configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"6 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"MCAL","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Well satisfied. We expect training on other topics for more details. Thank you!","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563940873103"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563940873103"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37d8b6a448170017a2fd7b"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"No enough time, 3 day seems like not enough to understand every"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"OS, Comstack, Overview","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not yet","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For Powertrain","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941046147"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941046147"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37d9cfa448170017a2fd7d"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":"I was unable to do most of the exercises due to PC/tool performance issues"},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Partially (Met expectations)"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Understanding the structure/layers","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Not worked yet","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941327365"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941327365"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37dc41a448170017a2fd7f"},"name":"Shoaib Ahmed Khan","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Exercises"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Mode management & memory stack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"COM & OBD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941953064"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563941953064"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37f7b4a493710017089078"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM stack hands on session","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"It would be goodif you can explain more examples during theory sessions","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For COM stack configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"-Basic information of different autosar layers\n-Com stack\n-SWC concepts\n- Hands-on on SWC\n- Gained some knowledge in the above","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563948980613"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563948980613"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37f7b4a493710017089079"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"0","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM stack hands on session","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"It would be goodif you can explain more examples during theory sessions","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"For COM stack configuration","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"-Basic information of different autosar layers\n-Com stack\n-SWC concepts\n- Hands-on on SWC\n- Gained some knowledge in the above","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563948980787"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563948980787"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37f9bda49371001708907a"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Explaination of our doubts"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Theory & practicals","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Good Training","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563949501248"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563949501248"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d37fa31a49371001708907b"},"name":"Surabhi","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":""}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Config, Com Stack, Diag Stack","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"3 months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Safety Library","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes :)","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563949617856"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563949617856"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d381bc3f9f98f00177bf65c"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Safety, diagnostics"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Config, Com","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"Six months","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"CDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes, well experienced trainers and organised training","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958211269"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958211269"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d381c25f9f98f00177bf65d"},"name":"Yogesh Patel","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Exercises"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"COM stack ","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"-","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"1 month","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"Autosar, CDD","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"Yes. It was really good.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958309711"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958309711"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d381e8bf9f98f00177bf65e"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"4","comments":"It is good"},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"One who dont know the subject, understanding might be difficult"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"Autosar","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"No","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"3","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"It is good with theoritical. Practically, it is difficult to understand.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958923257"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1563958923257"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d3968ead5417000174fc60b"},"name":"","training":"EB Tresos Classic AUTOSAR","trainers":"Tejinder Singh Sagar,Sivaram Nagarajan","location":"Siemens, Bangalore","date":"2019-07-17 to 2019-07-19","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"yes","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Presentation was very clear to understand"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"presentation & practical session;","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"5","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"YES, I am new to AUTOSAR, it was clear understanding for me.","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1564043498842"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1564043498842"}}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5d39f916ce62d80017f87895"},"name":"","training":"EB Guide","trainers":"Prashanth Dwarakanath,Mohamed Firdous","location":"Elektrobit","date":"2019-07-26 to 2019-07-28","questions":[{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to its contents?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Quality of content","rating":"1","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Value of content for you","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Relevance of exercises","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Logical structure and comprehensibility","rating":"4","comments":""}]},{"question":"How would you rate the quality of the training with regards to the trainer?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Presentation Skills","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Understandability of Explanations","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Product expertise","rating":"3","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Interaction with Participants","rating":"2","comments":""}]},{"question":"Did the training meet your expectations?","question_type":"yes or No","answer":"no","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"If yes, what did you like most? If no, where could improvements be made?","rating":"","comments":"Test Comment"}]},{"question":"Which was the most valuable part of the training?","question_type":"","answer":"q4","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Which topics were missing in the training?","question_type":"","answer":"k","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"How long did you already work with EB Product (Months r Years)","question_type":"","answer":"l","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"For which tasks do you use product?","question_type":"","answer":"m","comments":"","subquestions":[]},{"question":"Your overall training experiences?","question_type":"rating","answer":"","comments":"","subquestions":[{"sub_ques":"Recommendation pf this training to others","rating":"2","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall event organization","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Applicability of what I learned","rating":"4","comments":""},{"sub_ques":"Overall training experience","rating":"5","comments":""}]},{"question":"Are you satisfied with the training? We welcome your testimonial statement?","question_type":"","answer":"abc","comments":"","subquestions":[]}],"createdAt":{"$numberLong":"1564080406434"},"updatedAt":{"$numberLong":"1564080406434"}}
